<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://idan.goldman.work/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://idan.goldman.work/" rel="alternate" type="text/html"/><updated>2019-10-24T12:58:57+03:00</updated><id>https://idan.goldman.work/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Idan Goldman</title><subtitle>Experienced Frontend Developer</subtitle><author><name>idan_goldman</name></author><entry><title type="html">Month of Pivoting</title><link href="https://idan.goldman.work/notebook/month-of-pivoting/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Month of Pivoting"/><published>2019-08-05T21:01:00+03:00</published><updated>2019-10-16T01:24:09+03:00</updated><id>https://idan.goldman.work/notebook/month-of-pivoting</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://idan.goldman.work/notebook/month-of-pivoting/">&lt;p&gt;My month was split into two parts, before vacation and after.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;!-- more --&gt; &lt;h4 id=&quot;hello-how-was-your-month&quot;&gt;Hello, how was your month?&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt;My month was split into two parts, before vacation and after.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;YES! We went on a trip to Portugal for the second time. It was awesome as always! Good food, beaches, weather, alcohol, and one-stop at Starbucks for old times sake. See photos from the trip on my &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/idan.goldman/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt; account.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;With recharged energy, I have decided to move out of the apartment into &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wework.com/labs&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;WeWork Labs&lt;/a&gt; and do the product right by pivoting.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;pivoting-to-a-different-problem&quot;&gt;Pivoting to a Different Problem&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;The problem I have been trying to solve with a “Coming Soon Page Builder” product was not a real problem for my target audience because it already has a good enough solution. The product does solve a problem for a different audience that I’m not interested to pursue and develop a product in that direction.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Now what? Well, redefining the problem, a pivot. Whatever you say when you hit the wall with your product and need to change some stuff to move forward.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;market-research&quot;&gt;Market Research&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;The new problem is “designers, developers, and webmasters, spend a lot of time on moving the envelope from design to code to a content management system to the server. Also, they spend a lot of time on learning technologies for project X on demand from their clients”.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This problem led me to the question of “how to create a tool with design and code abilities to help designers, developers, and webmasters save time”.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Before running to write code while screaming various answers inside my head. I want to solve this problem right by first validating with designers, developers, webmasters that this is an actual problem.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;As I write these lines I’m interviewing people from the target audience to see if the problem and the solution are valid. Interviewing a crowd of 100 people will make me comfortable to decide if I have a valid case to proceed.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;current-month&quot;&gt;Current Month&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;So, this month I will be focusing on only one thing which is market research. Talking to people and see if I can help them solve a problem I think they have.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Wish me luck, fingers crossed!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;thanks-for-reading&quot;&gt;Thanks for reading!&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;The newsletter sent to 119 people on Monday before last and until today it achieved:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;46 (39%) opened.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;2 (4.3%) replied.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;1 (0.84%) unsubscribed.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Until next month&lt;/em&gt;, enjoy and let me know what you think! 🙌&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>idan_goldman</name></author><category term="newsletter"/><summary type="html">My month was split into two parts, before vacation and after.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Month of Flying By</title><link href="https://idan.goldman.work/notebook/month-of-flying-by/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Month of Flying By"/><published>2019-07-01T18:06:00+03:00</published><updated>2019-10-16T01:24:09+03:00</updated><id>https://idan.goldman.work/notebook/month-of-flying-by</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://idan.goldman.work/notebook/month-of-flying-by/">&lt;p&gt;It was a good and relaxing month for me, the “independence” part starting to sink in. Making me shift focus from doing only things that will bring immediate value to things that need more time to harvest. For example: meeting people, creating new connections, maintaining early ones too instead of building a web agency.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;!-- more --&gt; &lt;h4 id=&quot;hello-how-was-your-month&quot;&gt;Hello, how was your month?&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt;It was a good and relaxing month for me, the “independence” part starting to sink in. Making me shift focus from doing only things that will bring immediate value to things that need more time to harvest. For example: meeting people, creating new connections, maintaining early ones too instead of building a web agency.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This brings my next point, I have met a few interesting people this month and had the pleasure to be interviewed at &lt;a href=&quot;https://indietlv.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;IndieTLV&lt;/a&gt;’s Hack Night. This event happens every 2 weeks at the Google Campus in Tel Aviv, you should check it out! Oh, and you can watch the interview &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kMhQtl4VHv4&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; (in Hebrew).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Last thing, the &lt;a href=&quot;https://staticpage.io/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;new website&lt;/a&gt; is up and running.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;launch-and-forget&quot;&gt;Launch and Forget&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;In Israel, we use this idiom to describe automation. Create something of value (what does that even mean?), release it to the internet (what could possibly go wrong?), and interact with it only in the time of need (meaning never).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This what I was trying to achieve with automating my social media presence. 4 posts a week during work days on 2 social networks (Twitter, LinkedIn). 4 weeks in, I have achieved great success in the automation department only 30min of work every two weeks! BUT the engagement department suffered deeply with decreasing numbers. My guess, it’s because I have stopped engaging with others on those social networks. Also, most of the content created from socializing on those networks and now it’s almost gone!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;A guess, I will be going back to engaging on social media…&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;college-experience&quot;&gt;College Experience&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;It was hard for me to focus this month and do the work. Instead, I was more focused on household chores during work hours. I got pretty good at laundry, dishwashing, organizing, and taking the garbage out.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;None of those helped to move the product forward… So, I have decided to search for a “hot desk” in one of Tel Aviv’s workspaces. This will help place home/work boundaries and more importantly make me part of a community. A real one, where you need to interact with words and smiles, kind of college experience I never had.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;freelance-aint-free&quot;&gt;Freelance ain’t Free&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;I’m shutting down the whole Freelance Markets expedition until further notice. Fiverr REALLY not working for me and UpWork have a demand and supply volume which requires full-time attention. I prefer to spend that attention on making the next version of StaticPage based on users and friends feedback.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;current-month&quot;&gt;Current Month&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;So, this month I will be focusing on the following things:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Moving to a workspace&lt;/strong&gt;, meeting new people, networking and hearing out other people thoughts on StaticPage and the market.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Writing the specs&lt;/strong&gt; of the next version of StaticPage. Damn It’s going to be awesome!&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Finding freelancers&lt;/strong&gt; to help me build the next version of StaticPage. Not going to do this alone this time.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;thanks-for-reading&quot;&gt;Thanks for reading!&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;The newsletter sent to 122 people on Monday before last and until today it achieved:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;44 (36.4%) opened.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;4 (9.0%) replied.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;3 (2.45%) unsubscribed.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Until next month&lt;/em&gt;, enjoy and let me know what you think! 🙌&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>idan_goldman</name></author><category term="newsletter"/><summary type="html">It was a good and relaxing month for me, the “independence” part starting to sink in. Making me shift focus from doing only things that will bring immediate value to things that need more time to harvest. For example: meeting people, creating new connections, maintaining early ones too instead of building a web agency.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Month of learning</title><link href="https://idan.goldman.work/notebook/month-of-learning/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Month of learning"/><published>2019-06-03T18:45:00+03:00</published><updated>2019-10-16T01:24:09+03:00</updated><id>https://idan.goldman.work/notebook/month-of-learning</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://idan.goldman.work/notebook/month-of-learning/">&lt;p&gt;Mine went awesome! Learned about what people want in their page builder, keyword research, video editing, social media posting. Oh, and the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vEiAj0Zr5xc&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;walkthrough video&lt;/a&gt; is out!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;!-- more --&gt; &lt;h4 id=&quot;hello-how-was-your-month&quot;&gt;Hello, how was your month?&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt;Mine went awesome! Learned about what people want in their page builder, keyword research, video editing, social media posting. Oh, and the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vEiAj0Zr5xc&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;walkthrough video&lt;/a&gt; is out!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;marketing-on-fiverr&quot;&gt;Marketing on Fiverr&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;It’s not going well, had &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;62&lt;/strong&gt; Impressions&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;13&lt;/strong&gt; Clicks&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;34&lt;/strong&gt; Views&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1&lt;/strong&gt; Buyer Message&lt;/em&gt; for my Gig in the 2 weeks since it was posted. Tried to share the gig on my social media accounts &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:activity:6539187166130561024/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;LinkedIn&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/idan_goldman/status/1133443320162791424&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; as recommended by Fiverr and nothing changed.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;During the next 2 weeks&lt;/strong&gt;, I will be selling proactively on Fiverr. There is a “Buyer Requests” page on the site, where buyers can post their gig requests and Sellers can apply. Already applied for a “build static web page” gig.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What if this won’t work?&lt;/strong&gt; I’m off Fiverr to open UpWork or PeoplePerHour (Freelance markets like Fiverr) account and continue with the proactive approach. Applying for job offers to “build static web pages” of all sorts.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I’m using this technique for two reasons. First to understand better the needs and trends of the buying crowd. Second to understand the sellers’ crowd needs firsthand and what kind of tools will help them.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;creating-content&quot;&gt;Creating Content&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;Damn it’s hard! Writing is awesome but time-consuming and a real skill I hopefully will craft one day. But this is not what I wanted to talk to you about in this section. I had a Goal of publishing my first blog post by &lt;strong&gt;1st of June&lt;/strong&gt; and everything went according to plan &lt;strong&gt;UNTIL&lt;/strong&gt; I had a new plan.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The New Plan&lt;/strong&gt;, separate the website code from the application code and move the website code to the same one the blog is using. &lt;a href=&quot;https://jekyllrb.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt;, the codebase the blog is using if you were wondering.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This change taking more time than expected but it’s a positive one. Combining the website and the blog under the same roof (content management system) is a good thing for search engine optimization, content editing, design editing, code writing, and especially for new sections like documentation and support (more about those in the next Newsletter 😉).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;social-media-updates&quot;&gt;Social Media Updates&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;This was a good social media month! Twitter numbers got +100% increase and I’m excited to grow the account even further this month. Also, I have tried sharing content on LinkedIn starting last week and still don’t know what to make of it. I even opened my first business social account on Instagram. It’s the perfect platform to create a community around a visual product like StaticPage. Waiting until next week to create and publish content on Instagram.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;All this social media activity wasn’t possible without automating the process of sharing on social networks. I’m sharing 1-2 posts a day, 4 days a week (Mon-Thu) on Twitter and LinkedIn. This would take me hours every day if I would do it by hand! Thankfully, there are ways to automate this! One of the ways is to use &lt;a href=&quot;https://buffer.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Buffer&lt;/a&gt; (social media management platform).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;current-month&quot;&gt;Current Month&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;I have decided to move the newsletter update for a monthly one. The biggest reason for the change is: it’s hard for me to write fast and it’s taking me half a day to a day to make the newsletter. Moving it to once a month task will clear time to do other tasks and make the content of the newsletter better.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;So, this month I will be focusing on the following things:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Releasing the blog&lt;/strong&gt; by finishing building it and writing the first blog post. Have any idea what the first blog post should be about? Let me know!&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Applying daily for Buyer Requests&lt;/strong&gt; on Fiverr to get my first gig.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Opening UpWork or PeoplePerHour account&lt;/strong&gt; and applying to job offerings to build static web pages.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Social media growth&lt;/strong&gt; by generating and posting more content onto it. Also, talk to people on Social networks about StaticPage and hear their feedback.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;thanks-for-reading&quot;&gt;Thanks for reading!&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;The newsletter sent to 122 people on last Monday and until today it achieved:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;48 (39.7%) opened.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;4 (8.3%) replied.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;4 (8.3%) clicked on links.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;0 subscribed.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;1 (0.8%) unsubscribed.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Until next week&lt;/em&gt;, enjoy and let me know what you think! 🙌&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>idan_goldman</name></author><category term="newsletter"/><summary type="html">Mine went awesome! Learned about what people want in their page builder, keyword research, video editing, social media posting. Oh, and the walkthrough video is out!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Week of Quiet</title><link href="https://idan.goldman.work/notebook/week-of-quiet/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Week of Quiet"/><published>2019-05-20T16:00:00+03:00</published><updated>2019-10-16T01:24:09+03:00</updated><id>https://idan.goldman.work/notebook/week-of-quiet</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://idan.goldman.work/notebook/week-of-quiet/">&lt;p&gt;Mine went good all things considered except the routine which went to hell. I’m partially back to work! Re-recorded StaticPage’s walkthrough video. Published Fiverr gig “Create a Coming Soon Page in 1 Day”. Got more traction on Twitter with the help of a pen pal, and got deeper into the rabbit hole of productivity apps.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;!-- more --&gt; &lt;h4 id=&quot;hello-how-were-your-last-two-weeks&quot;&gt;Hello, how were your last two weeks?&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt;Mine went good all things considered except the routine which went to hell. I’m partially back to work! Re-recorded StaticPage’s walkthrough video. Published Fiverr gig “Create a Coming Soon Page in 1 Day”. Got more traction on Twitter with the help of a pen pal, and got deeper into the rabbit hole of productivity apps.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;todos-management&quot;&gt;Todos Management&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;As you know, I have left Trello for old school pen and paper. Which are great for short term daily tasks, but get messy after a few days. That is why I’m testing &lt;a href=&quot;https://todoist.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Todoist&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://ticktick.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;TickTick&lt;/a&gt; todo lists managers. Each one has its own advantages, for example, TickTick has more features. Like todo description, calendar integration, Pomodoro timer built in. On the other hand, Todoist is much simpler, better known (community support), and has Karma points. Every time you check something off the list Todoist gives you some Karma points which seems meaningless at first but motivating in the long term!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bottom line&lt;/strong&gt;, I need more time to test and decide which one is best for me.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;fiverr-gig&quot;&gt;Fiverr Gig&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;Posted yesterday my first gig on Fiverr titled “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fiverr.com/idan_goldman/create-a-coming-soon-page-in-1-day&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Create a Coming Soon Page in 1 Day&lt;/a&gt;”. The gig is all about creating a Coming Soon page for $20 using StaticPage. In the end, the buyer will get the coming soon page and a StaticPage account to play around with. This week, I will be promoting this gig on LinkedIn and Twitter might help land my first buyer.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;P.S.&lt;/strong&gt; I have missed a goal deadline on this one by a week and two marketplaces. The goal was on “May 13th, Official release of Fiverr, Upwork, PeoplePerHour seller accounts”.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;social-media&quot;&gt;Social Media&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;I’m getting more traction on Twitter by sharing my experience and knowledge as a developer with beginner developers. I’m trying to help them overcome their fear of code, not knowing everything by memory, and actual code problems. This wouldn’t have been possible without my pen pal &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/YuriSpiridonov&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;@YuriSpiridonov&lt;/a&gt; who shares a lot of my tweets with his followers. Next, I will try to do the same on LinkedIn.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;current-week&quot;&gt;Current week&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;This week I will be focusing on the following things:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Promoting my Fiverr gig&lt;/strong&gt; on social media channels until I will get the first buyer.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Leaning more about what works&lt;/strong&gt; on social media in terms of engagement and traffic. Focusing on Twitter and LinkedIn only.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Continue working on the walkthrough video&lt;/strong&gt; “How to: Create a Coming Soon page with StaticPage”. Hopefully will be done with it by next week.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;thanks-for-reading&quot;&gt;Thanks for reading!&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;The newsletter sent to 123 people on last Monday and until today it achieved:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;53 (43.8%) opened.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;7 (13.2%) replied. Thank you for the love! :)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;0 clicked on links.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;0 subscribed.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;1 (0.8%) unsubscribed.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;Waiting to see next week’s numbers!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Until next week&lt;/em&gt;, enjoy and let me know what you think! 🙌&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>idan_goldman</name></author><category term="newsletter"/><summary type="html">Mine went good all things considered except the routine which went to hell. I’m partially back to work! Re-recorded StaticPage’s walkthrough video. Published Fiverr gig “Create a Coming Soon Page in 1 Day”. Got more traction on Twitter with the help of a pen pal, and got deeper into the rabbit hole of productivity apps.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Week of Rest</title><link href="https://idan.goldman.work/notebook/week-of-rest/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Week of Rest"/><published>2019-05-06T16:18:00+03:00</published><updated>2019-10-16T01:24:09+03:00</updated><id>https://idan.goldman.work/notebook/week-of-rest</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://idan.goldman.work/notebook/week-of-rest/">&lt;p&gt;Mine went great, deployed the new landing page on time, talked with some of you, got great advice, and even worked a bit on the upcoming video. Then I had to go through a small medical procedure that took me “out of order” for the rest of the week and from the looks of it this week too.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;!-- more --&gt; &lt;h4 id=&quot;hello-how-was-your-week&quot;&gt;Hello, how was your week?&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt;Mine went great, deployed the new landing page on time, talked with some of you, got great advice, and even worked a bit on the upcoming video. Then I had to go through a small medical procedure that took me “out of order” for the rest of the week and from the looks of it this week too.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Now, I’m following the doctor’s orders: staying in bed, walking around the house, and eating well. Which makes me crazy but hey! I want to get better fast and go back to doing what I’m doing.. creating a great product company!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Until next week or month&lt;/em&gt;, enjoy and let me know what you think! 🙌&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>idan_goldman</name></author><category term="newsletter"/><summary type="html">Mine went great, deployed the new landing page on time, talked with some of you, got great advice, and even worked a bit on the upcoming video. Then I had to go through a small medical procedure that took me “out of order” for the rest of the week and from the looks of it this week too.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Week of Holidays</title><link href="https://idan.goldman.work/notebook/week-of-holidays/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Week of Holidays"/><published>2019-04-29T16:58:00+03:00</published><updated>2019-10-16T01:24:09+03:00</updated><id>https://idan.goldman.work/notebook/week-of-holidays</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://idan.goldman.work/notebook/week-of-holidays/">&lt;p&gt;My went great, spend some family and got some work done using the new routine tools for last week’s update. Let’s see some stats today!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;!-- more --&gt; &lt;h4 id=&quot;hello-how-did-you-spend-your-holiday-season&quot;&gt;Hello, how did you spend your holiday season?&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt;My went great, spend some family and got some work done using the new routine tools for last week’s update. Let’s see some stats today!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;routine-stats&quot;&gt;Routine Stats&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;Last week I wrote about changing my work routine and using some tools to help me enforce and track that work routine. A week past and here my results so far:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Started with &lt;strong&gt;15 blocked websites&lt;/strong&gt; and now I’m at &lt;strong&gt;26 blocked websites&lt;/strong&gt;. Enabled working hours to block those websites between 10am to 9pm.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Worked on average &lt;strong&gt;9.4 pomodoros per day (4.7h)&lt;/strong&gt; this week. Not including talking to potential users, researching competitors, and talking with friends that help me with web design and video editing.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;I have &lt;strong&gt;meditated 4 out of 7 days&lt;/strong&gt; this week.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Positive&lt;/strong&gt;, the stats are good for a first week especially with holidays and all. This Pomodoro technique® and blocked websites gave me a framework to work in and focus! Also, I’m starting to get a sense of how much time I’m spending on each task. Can see how it will benefit me in the future.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Negative&lt;/strong&gt;, A bit bummed out about the meditation, might be the holidays, might be just me struggling with it. But I’m not worried about it at the moment. Also, stopped using &lt;a href=&quot;https://trello.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Trello&lt;/a&gt; for task management, back to using pen and paper. Crossing items off the list manually.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;may-1st-release&quot;&gt;May 1st Release&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;The work on a new landing page for StaticPage is done with the help of a friend which is a brilliant web and product designer. The work on the new video for the landing page continues with the help of a skillful artistic friend. Don’t worry the video won’t have any 3D effects. We are trying to make it as professional as possible and it takes time, that is why it might not be ready for the May 1st release. With that written the new landing page will be launched on time! Worst case scenario the video will be replaced couple of days later.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;current-week&quot;&gt;Current week&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;This week I will be focusing on the following things:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Writing a product release&lt;/strong&gt; part of May 1st release to StaticPage users and mailing list members announcing new landing page, video, and templates feature.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Start working on marketing&lt;/strong&gt; myself as an expert building landing pages or coming soon pages on Fiverr. Trying to land my first gig and do it with the help of StaticPage.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;thanks-for-reading&quot;&gt;Thanks for reading!&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;The newsletter sent to 129 people on last Monday and until today it achieved:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;51 (40.5%) opened.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;6 (11.7%) replied, 2 of them “on - vacation” auto-replies. :D&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;3 (5.8%) clicked on links.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;1 (0.8%) subscribed.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;5 (3.8%) unsubscribed.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;Waiting to see next week’s numbers!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h3 id=&quot;following-me-and-the-landing-page-competition&quot;&gt;Following me and the landing page competition?&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;p&gt;Yeah, I’m not going to win. So, I have dropped from the competition and moved all the contacts &lt;a href=&quot;https://convertkit.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;ConvertKit&lt;/a&gt; to &lt;a href=&quot;https://mailchimp.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Mailchimp&lt;/a&gt;. See you at the product release!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Until next week&lt;/em&gt;, enjoy and let me know what you think! 🙌&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>idan_goldman</name></author><category term="newsletter"/><summary type="html">My went great, spend some family and got some work done using the new routine tools for last week’s update. Let’s see some stats today!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Week of Change</title><link href="https://idan.goldman.work/notebook/week-of-change/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Week of Change"/><published>2019-04-22T16:22:00+03:00</published><updated>2019-10-16T01:24:09+03:00</updated><id>https://idan.goldman.work/notebook/week-of-change</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://idan.goldman.work/notebook/week-of-change/">&lt;p&gt;My week went solid. Released a StaticPage templates feature and instead of continuing to build a new landing page. I took a step back and thought about my near future goals and working routine.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;!-- more --&gt; &lt;h4 id=&quot;hello-how-was-your-week&quot;&gt;Hello, how was your week?&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt;My week went solid. Released a StaticPage templates feature and instead of continuing to build a new landing page. I took a step back and thought about my near future goals and working routine.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;work-routine&quot;&gt;Work Routine&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;I had to change some stuff in my work routine. Working long hours in chaos might be cool at the moment but won’t help me in the long run. Especially when new and old media distractions are a click away. A cup of tea in my right hand and phone in my left, I have decided to make some changes.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;First thing first&lt;/strong&gt;, for any good routine to work it has to start with an information diet. NO social networks, NO news sites, NO entertainment or game sites during work hours. &lt;a href=&quot;https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/site-blocker/ccachieepekabdbcpfegamckdidpepga&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Site blocker&lt;/a&gt; is a chrome extension helping me with the task of blocking distracting sites. The count of blocked sites stands on 15 at the moment.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Second thing&lt;/strong&gt;, for any good routine to work it has to have a pace. What better to measure time and give pace than &lt;a href=&quot;https://francescocirillo.com/pages/pomodoro-technique&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Pomodoro Technique®&lt;/a&gt;. I will be doing 12 pomodoros of 30 minutes each a day with optional breaks of 5 or 15 minutes in between. &lt;a href=&quot;https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/marinara-pomodoro%C2%AE-assist/lojgmehidjdhhbmpjfamhpkpodfcodef&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Marinara: Pomodoro® Assistant&lt;/a&gt; is a chrome extension helping me with the task of work pacing.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Third thing&lt;/strong&gt;, for any routine to work the mind has to be in favor of it. How can I train the brain to be on my side? Meditation comes to mind. I have tried it once before and it did wonders for me. I will do it once a day, every morning for 10 minutes. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.headspace.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Headspace&lt;/a&gt; is a mindfulness phone app helping me with the task of thoughts balance and peace.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I can feel you screaming at me, SPORTS!!! You should do sports! Yeah, I know, I should and I will. As better people before me said: “one step at the time”. First, I will learn how to do this routine and then I will add more complex actions to it.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;It’s not easy, I can tell you that! But it’s worth it. I will update you on the progress with some stats next week.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;near-future-goals&quot;&gt;Near future goals&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;Part of the chaos surrounding me was not having clear goals for the near future. Besides the one at the end of the month and keeping you updated. At which, I’m doing a pretty consistent job! But, I do need more goals at least for the next couple of months to keep moving forward. So, I did a little soul digging and come up with a few goals that will promote StaticPage as a product and me as a creator and a provider. Here they are:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;May 1st&lt;/strong&gt;, Launch a StaticPage landing page with services provided and a walkthrough video.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;May 13th&lt;/strong&gt;, Have an active seller account on these freelance markets: Fiverr, Upwork, PeoplePerHour.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;June 1st&lt;/strong&gt;, Write a first blog post in a while with that expand StaticPage’s and my audience.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;June 20th&lt;/strong&gt;, Get 20 users for StaticPage.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;July 1st&lt;/strong&gt;, Build a paywall for StaticPage with the ability to try before you buy.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;August 1st&lt;/strong&gt;, New version of StaticPage on top of user feedback.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;August 8st&lt;/strong&gt;, StaticPage press release on tech release websites&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;What do you think? Am I going in the right direction?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;current-week&quot;&gt;Current week&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;This week I will be focusing on the following things:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Create a better landing page&lt;/strong&gt; for StaticPage instead of the one I’m using for the competition. &lt;strong&gt;Create a better walkthrough video&lt;/strong&gt; for StaticPage, including how to create of a landing page, preset templates, and hip background music.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;thanks-for-reading&quot;&gt;Thanks for reading!&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;The newsletter sent to 134 people on last Monday and until today it achieved:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;65 (49.2%) opened.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;2 (3%) replied.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;1 (0.8%) clicked on links.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;0 (0%) subscribed to the landing page.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;5 (3.7%) unsubscribed.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;Waiting to see next week’s numbers!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h3 id=&quot;still-reading-and-want-to-support-me&quot;&gt;Still reading and want to support me?&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;p&gt;Please subscribe to StaticPage testing mailing list here: &lt;del&gt;bit.ly/GetStaticPage&lt;/del&gt; and help win $5k which will help growing StaticPage.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Until next week&lt;/em&gt;, enjoy and let me know what you think! 🙌&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>idan_goldman</name></author><category term="newsletter"/><summary type="html">My week went solid. Released a StaticPage templates feature and instead of continuing to build a new landing page. I took a step back and thought about my near future goals and working routine.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Feedback Week</title><link href="https://idan.goldman.work/notebook/feedback-week/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Feedback Week"/><published>2019-04-15T17:01:00+03:00</published><updated>2019-10-16T01:24:09+03:00</updated><id>https://idan.goldman.work/notebook/feedback-week</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://idan.goldman.work/notebook/feedback-week/">&lt;p&gt;My week went horribly with the wrong marketing assumptions, followed by anxiety. On the bright side, templates feature for StaticPage is almost ready for release with 4 templates. Now, ready to retrospec and move forward.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;!-- more --&gt; &lt;h4 id=&quot;hello-how-was-your-week&quot;&gt;Hello, how was your week?&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt;My week went horribly with the wrong marketing assumptions, followed by anxiety. On the bright side, templates feature for StaticPage is almost ready for release with 4 templates. Now, ready to retrospec and move forward.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;what-am-i-doing&quot;&gt;What am I doing?&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;During the week some of you expressed concern on the subject of &lt;strong&gt;we are happy for you but what the hell are you doing?!&lt;/strong&gt; Thanks for asking and sorry for not being clear about it. I’m doing two things, here they are:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;First thing&lt;/strong&gt;, Making *landing pages for a living. If you need a landing page built, let me know I’m your guy!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Second thing&lt;/strong&gt;, building a product named &lt;strong&gt;StaticPage&lt;/strong&gt;. A landing page builder like Wix but better! How better? It takes fewer steps to create a landing page with it. You can download the code and host the landing page wherever you want. Another advantage, you get support from me as quickly as humanly possible and not from a corporate middle man.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;*Landing page is a web page that a business owner wants to drive people to. This web page can be: new website opening, sale for a holiday, product release, etc…&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;thanks-for-reading&quot;&gt;Thanks for reading!&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;Let’s continue with the most important subject, your numbers. The newsletter sent to 140 people on last Monday and until today it achieved:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;63 (46.7%) opened.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;4 (6.3%) replied.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;3 (2.2%) clicked on links.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;3 (100%) subscribed to the landing page.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;6 (4.2%) unsubscribed.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;Interesting to see what’s the numbers will be this week.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;failed-marketing-assumptions&quot;&gt;Failed marketing assumptions&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;Before starting StaticPage marketing, when someone would ask me about “how would I market StaticPage to the right audience?”. I would brag that it’s simple. My audience is freelancers. So, I just need to sign up to the freelance marketplaces and send them a message. They will love StaticPage!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Boy, I was wrong&lt;/strong&gt;. I have signed up to 3 freelance marketplaces and not only my messages weren’t appealing as much as I thought. Also, I have violated the Terms of Service on all the marketplaces and was blocked.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;At the moment I’m trying to think of alternative ways reaching those freelancers. Facebook groups and Twitter came to mind. Do you have any other suggestions?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;preview-of-staticpage-templates&quot;&gt;Preview of StaticPage templates&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;Failing marketing gave me the energy to work on StaticPage’s code! I’m proud to release this week a templates feature. Meaning, every time you create a new landing page with StaticPage. You will be able to pick 1 of 4 cool templates to begin with:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/notebook/2019-04-15-feedback-week/back-to-school.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Back to School Template Screenshot&quot; /&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Back to School&lt;/strong&gt; template with a Countdown clock.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/notebook/2019-04-15-feedback-week/localbar.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;LocalBar Template Screenshot&quot; /&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LocalBar&lt;/strong&gt; template with Social Icons.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/notebook/2019-04-15-feedback-week/goooal.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Gooal Template Screenshot&quot; /&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GOOOAL!&lt;/strong&gt; template with a Mailing list.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/notebook/2019-04-15-feedback-week/flight-club.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Flight Club Template Screenshot&quot; /&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Flight Club&lt;/strong&gt; template with a Countdown clock, Mailing list, and Social Icons.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;current-week&quot;&gt;Current week&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;This week is all about focusing on these things:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Releasing StaticPage’s templates feature.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Working on a landing page that will explain better what StaticPage is and what I do.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;h3 id=&quot;still-reading-and-want-to-support-me&quot;&gt;Still reading and want to support me?&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;p&gt;Please subscribe to StaticPage testing mailing list here: &lt;del&gt;bit.ly/GetStaticPage&lt;/del&gt; and help win $5k which will help growing StaticPage.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Until next week&lt;/em&gt;, enjoy and let me know what you think! 🙌&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>idan_goldman</name></author><category term="newsletter"/><summary type="html">My week went horribly with the wrong marketing assumptions, followed by anxiety. On the bright side, templates feature for StaticPage is almost ready for release with 4 templates. Now, ready to retrospec and move forward.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">First week of spreading the word</title><link href="https://idan.goldman.work/notebook/first-week-of-spreading-the-word/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="First week of spreading the word"/><published>2019-04-08T15:43:00+03:00</published><updated>2019-10-16T01:24:09+03:00</updated><id>https://idan.goldman.work/notebook/first-week-of-spreading-the-word</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://idan.goldman.work/notebook/first-week-of-spreading-the-word/">&lt;p&gt;My week went fine with some initial numbers to show for, now I’m ready and excited for this week’s tasks!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;!-- more --&gt; &lt;h4 id=&quot;hello-again-how-was-your-week&quot;&gt;Hello again, how was your week?&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TL;DR&lt;/strong&gt; My week went fine with some initial numbers to show for, now I’m ready and excited for this week’s tasks!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;how-well-the-first-newsletter-was-received&quot;&gt;How well the first Newsletter was received?&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;Let’s start with the most important numbers, your numbers. But first I want to thank you all for reading, subscribing, replying, and generally showing love. &lt;strong&gt;Thank you!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The newsletter sent to 150 people on last Monday and until today it achieved:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;95 (67.9%) opened.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;21 (15%) clicked on links.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;7 (33.3%) subscribed to the landing page.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;6 (6.3%) replied.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;3 (2%) unsubscribed.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;7 (4.6%) broken email. Not bad for a first week writing to a loving audience.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;pitching-to-sellers&quot;&gt;Pitching to Sellers&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;After the first day’s high sending out the newsletter, re-posting it on LinkedIn and Twitter. I was ready to talk to some potential beta testing customers or sellers as Fiverr calls them.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The measurement&lt;/strong&gt; used for finding these sellers was:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;em&gt;Should have “I Will create a Coming Soon page for you” gig with above 10 recommendations&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The pitch flow&lt;/em&gt; was to approach 50 Fiverr sellers with a cold message, if they respond positively, then send them a link to the landing page. From there, they should decide to subscribe or not.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Have sent 3 cold messages before realizing the pitch flow was broken but more on this later. Fixed the pitch flow and successfully sent another 27 cold messages before Fiverr stopped me. They sent a parental notice that I’m in violation of their terms of use agreement and I should stop immediately. Made sense, so, I did.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Anyhow&lt;/strong&gt;, enough with the chit-chat, here are the pitching to sellers stats:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;30 messages were sent.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;23 (79.3%) were interested and got the link to the landing page.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;2 (8.6%) subscribed to the mailing list.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;2 (100%) register to test StaticPage.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Demographic split: Bangladesh (10), Pakistan (7), India (5), Sri Lanka (3), Serbia (2), Kuwait (1), Malaysia (1), US (1).&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;1 Bug fixed.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;h3 id=&quot;my-conclusions&quot;&gt;My conclusions:&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;The landing page should be optimized.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Most of the Coming Soon page sellers on Fiverr live in Eastern countries. I will have to overcome cultural and language barriers for me to successfully market to them.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;the-broken-pitch-flow&quot;&gt;The Broken Pitch Flow&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;I have started cold messaging sellers without a plan on what to respond to an interested seller, who knew they would?! For the first 3 interested sellers, I responded with 2 links. One to the landing page and the second to &lt;strong&gt;StaticPage&lt;/strong&gt; registration page. Realizing that having multiple links is a mistake and I should be sending only one link instead was an AH-HA moment of hindsight thinking.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I have quickly (took me the rest of the day) started changing the landing page content and flow. In a way that after subscribing to the mailing list, the seller will get an email with the link to register as a beta tester on StaticPage.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;*The visual and system bugs with the mailing list software (but hey I’m in a contest for $5k) did not help and only delayed the continuing of cold messaging Fiverr sellers.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;current-week&quot;&gt;Current week&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;This week is all about focusing on these things:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Send old StaticPage users an email about the revival of the product.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Approaching freelancers in the market of PeoplePerHour.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Deploy a Templates feature. This feature will help start new pages with preset of content.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Creating and submitting an ad to MakerAds advertising network. An ad network for indie makers. It’s free for makers, so why not?&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;h3 id=&quot;still-reading-and-want-to-support-me&quot;&gt;Still reading and want to support me?&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;p&gt;Please subscribe to StaticPage testing mailing list here: &lt;del&gt;bit.ly/GetStaticPage&lt;/del&gt; and help win $5k which will help growing StaticPage.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Until next week&lt;/em&gt;, enjoy and let me know what you think! 🙌&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>idan_goldman</name></author><category term="newsletter"/><summary type="html">My week went fine with some initial numbers to show for, now I’m ready and excited for this week’s tasks!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">April Fool’s Beginning</title><link href="https://idan.goldman.work/notebook/april-fools-beginning/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="April Fool's Beginning"/><published>2019-04-01T16:40:00+03:00</published><updated>2019-10-16T01:24:09+03:00</updated><id>https://idan.goldman.work/notebook/april-fools-beginning</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://idan.goldman.work/notebook/april-fools-beginning/">&lt;p&gt;I’m starting a journey as a Bootstrapper and will be launching a product on May 1st.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;!-- more --&gt; &lt;h4 id=&quot;hello-friends-family-and-people-i-met-along-the-way&quot;&gt;Hello friends, family, and people I met along the way!&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TL;DR&lt;/strong&gt; I’m starting a journey as a Bootstrapper and will be launching a product on May 1st.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;fresh-start&quot;&gt;Fresh Start&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;After 10+ years in the tech industry as a FrontEnd/WordPress/BackEnd guy, I have decided to quit my job and follow the dream of creating a remote product company.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Lots of different product ideas floating in my head that I would love to see (and use) in the market today. Turing one of these ideas into a real product will be my main focus in the following months. Also, I will be writing about the journey of taking this product to market.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;So, what is the product you ask? A product that I have been working on over 3 years (on/off, mostly off) and some of you are probably tired hearing about it.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;StaticPage&lt;/strong&gt; is a page builder made for creating &lt;em&gt;Coming Soon&lt;/em&gt; pages with features like a countdown clock, social icons, MailChimp integration. Oh, and the ability to download the page and publish it on any hosting provider you want. I know it’s not much, but it’s only the beginning!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;You can enjoy watching an old demo video of &lt;strong&gt;StaticPage&lt;/strong&gt; here:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IKsY3fVeoa0&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IKsY3fVeoa0&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The marketing efforts will be focused on &lt;em&gt;Door-to-Door&lt;/em&gt; marketing to page building sellers on freelance markets like Fiverr, as Paul Graham famously said: “&lt;a href=&quot;http://paulgraham.com/ds.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Do things that Don’t Scale&lt;/a&gt;”.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;commitment&quot;&gt;Commitment&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;I will be launching &lt;strong&gt;StaticPage&lt;/strong&gt; on &lt;em&gt;May 1st&lt;/em&gt;, with all the irony it being the Worker’s Day and all.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;What’s stopping me from going back on the promise to you, delivering &lt;strong&gt;StaticPage&lt;/strong&gt; in one month? A lifetime commitment to you! OK, not a lifetime but a weekly one. Every Monday, an email update will be sent out describing the progress that been made that week. The extremists can get a daily progress update by following me on &lt;em&gt;Twitter&lt;/em&gt; (&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/idan_goldman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;@idan_goldman&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;help-out&quot;&gt;Help Out&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;Still reading and want to support me? I have entered a landing page contest to win &lt;strong&gt;$5k&lt;/strong&gt;! Winning it will help growing &lt;strong&gt;StaticPage&lt;/strong&gt; as a product and you can help too! Click on the link: &lt;del&gt;https://bit.ly/GetStaticPage&lt;/del&gt; to the landing page I have created as part of this contest. Type your email in the form, click on “Get Early Access” button and you are done. Thank you for your endorsement!!!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Until next week, enjoy and let me know what you think! 🙌&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;P.S.&lt;/strong&gt; if you don’t want to hear from me ever again, just hit that unsubscribe button below. Cya.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>idan_goldman</name></author><category term="newsletter"/><summary type="html">I’m starting a journey as a Bootstrapper and will be launching a product on May 1st.</summary></entry></feed>